Here's the exit.
Are you trying to kill me?
No, just trying to save us some time.
You and your shortcuts.
Wait a sec.
Do you even know where
this meeting's happening?
Yeah, I'll check.
Northwest inside that
mountain how much time we
got 20 minutes then we're
not going fast enough
I can't wait for you to see a miracle.
I can't wait for you.
I can't wait for you to see the future.
I'll reach the sky above the sky.
I'll reach the future of the future.
I wish we could go faster,
because at this rate we're not going
to make it before the Salamanders.
I know.
Even if we can warn them, it doesn't mean
we'll get the Commanders out in time.
We just might end up dying
with them all in battle.
I've got player readings!
68 of them flying in formation!
From what I can tell, it could
be the Salamander Attack Squad!
There are 14 more players on the plateau.
Most likely they're the diplomats
from the Sylphs and Catsies.
The two groups of players will
make contact in 50 seconds.
We didn't make it after all.
Thanks for trying, Kirito.
But this is far enough.
I'm gonna try and save Sakuya.
Get out of here and
head for the World Tree.
We didn't get to hang out
for long, but it was fun.
Hope we meet again someday.
Sorry, but running away from
a fight's not really my style.
Why are the salamanders here?
Salamanders, stand down! Who's that?
Sakuya!
Letha, what are you doing here?
It's too complicated to get into
now, but you see that guy out there?
Believe it or not, the fates of
our races depend on his next move.
You have got to be kidding.
I want to talk to your commander!
What the hell is a Spriggan
like you doing here?
I'm gonna kill you no
matter what your answer.
But since you're brave enough to face
me, I might as well hear you out.
My name is Kirito.
I'm an ambassador for the
Spriggan-Undine Alliance.
Since you're on the offensive today,
I'm assuming you want to wage a
full-on war between all our races.
The Undines are allied
with the Spriggans, huh?
And you're supposed to be their ambassador,
but you've come here without a guard?
Yeah, that's right. So what?
I was sent here to negotiate trade
terms with the Sylphs and the Catseed.
But if you interrupt our talks, you're
going to get to feel some serious hurt.
All of our races are going to team up,
and we'll bring the fight
straight to the salamanders.
You're kidding me, right?
You're all alone, and
you've got crappy gear,
so there's no way you could
be anyone's ambassador.
If you can survive my
attacks for 30 seconds,
then I'll believe you
are who you say you are.
Gee, thanks.
That's mighty generous.
This is bad. Why?
Do you see that salamander's sword?
It's the demon sword, Graham.
You need a two-handed sword
skill of 950 to equip it.
950?
Yes, and there's only one
person I know who can use it.
General Eugene.
Have you heard of him?
Yeah, I know the name.
He's the younger brother of Mortimer,
the leader of the salamanders.
They're brothers in real life, too.
Mortimer's a brilliant strategist,
but in terms of sheer power,
they say Eugene is the
game's strongest player.
Oh, no.
He's the strongest player?
Kirito...
What was that?
The ethereal shift.
The sword's bonus skill.
Whenever someone tries to block
it with a shield or sword,
the Demonic Swordgram can
phase right through it!
Really?
No way!
Can't believe you're not dead.
What the hell kind of attack was this?
Damn, he's good.
Hey, Big Red, I think your
30 seconds are up by now.
I've changed my mind.
I've decided to kill you anyway.
Now you have to survive until I do.
Yeah, that figures.
But I won't go down that easy.
This won't end well.
They both seem like equally skilled fighters,
but Eugene's weapon is far superior.
He can do it.
Kirito can beat him, I know it.
Ah!
Oh!
Whoa!
Uh!
I need to borrow this for a sec!
Kirito?
A few seconds, that's all you've bought!
Hey, where'd he go?
Do you think he ran away?
Of course he didn't!
As long as I'm alive, I'm not going
to let anyone in my party die.
I won't let that happen again.
Kirito would never run away and leave us.
Kirito!
Die!
No!
Splendid! Marvelous!
That was the most amazing fight ever!
Nice way done, Spriggan! Yeah!
That was good!
Yeah, seriously.
You're an excellent fighter.
In fact, you're the most
powerful player I've ever seen!
Well done.
You're not so bad yourself.
I didn't know the Spriggans had someone?
unlike you in their ranks.
This world's a bigger
place than I thought.
Are we cool then?
Will you withdraw?
Eugene, may I have a word?
Kagemune, what is it?
Him again.
Oh, then next time I'll make
sure to bring more friends along.
You might find this interesting.
You know how my party was
wiped out yesterday? So?
Well, this Spriggan, he's the
same guy who took everyone out.
And he was traveling with an undine.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Then I guess I have to believe you.
But just for the record,
the last thing our leader and I want is to
go to war with the Spriggans and Undines.
We'll withdraw for now, but I'm going to
be looking forward to fighting you again.
Then that makes two of us.
I guess some salamanders can
be cool after all. Who knew?
You really are insane, you know that?
Yeah, I get that a lot.
Excuse me, but could either of
you explain what's going on?
I see I could tell there was something
off about Sigurd's attitude recently.
He seemed so irritated
irritated about what
my guess he was
dissatisfied about the state
of Things that in terms
of power he couldn't
accept we'd fallen behind the Salamanders.
Power is very important
to a man like Sigurd and
not just for his abilities
and character stats.
but also as a player.
He craves power.
Yeah, but even so, why would he
turn spy for the salamanders?
It must have something to do with the 5.0
update that's going to be released soon.
I heard a rumor that they'll be
putting in a reincarnation system.
No way!
I'm sure Mortimer made him an offer.
Bring me the head of your leader and
I'll reincarnate you as a salamander.
So now what?
What'll you do, Sakuya?
Rue, have you raised your
dark magic skill yet? Mm-hmm.
Open a moonlight mirror to Sigurd.
Sigurd!
Sakuya!
Nice to see you, too.
Unfortunately I'm still alive how I mean
what happened at the meeting it went.
Very well there's still the matter of
signing the treaty though by the way we
had an unexpected guest what guest his
name is General Eugene and he sends his.
Leafa.
So that's it.
Those incompetent lizards.
Well, it's your move now, Sapia.
Are you going to find me?
Or maybe you want to take away my command.
If so, remember, without me running your
military, your rule won't last very long.
Actually, I was thinking of
granting the request you made them.
Since you can't stand being
a self, you're free to go.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Are you crazy?
Me?
You're banishing me?
I'm letting you live to wander the
neutral territory as a renegade.
With any luck, you'll find something
there that'll occupy your precious time.
You bi -
Sakuya?
Thank you for saving us, Leafa.
You've no idea how grateful
I am having you around.
Oh, well, I didn't really do anything.
If you want to thank
someone, thank Kirito.
She's right.
Whoever you are, you have my thanks.
Hey, handsome.
About the Spriggan and
Dean ambassador business...
You aren't, are you?
Uh...
Yeah, that was a big fat lie.
I was bluffing, conning,
you know, negotiating.
Oh god, you must be insane.
You have to be to make all that
stuff up at the last minute.
Yeah, but it worked, didn't it?
Whenever I'm dealt a bad
hand, I always raise the pot.
You know, for a big fat liar, you're
pretty freaking strong, handsome.
You're like the MVP of Spriggans.
Are you their secret weapon?
Nah, of course not.
All I am is your friendly
neighborhood mercenary.
I like the wandering type.
Have you ever thought about
being a merc for the cat scene?
You get three meals a day
plus snacks and a nap.
So, Kirito, I was thinking, how about we
get to know each other a little better?
I know a cute little pub
in Sylvain. My treat.
Wait!
Aw, come on, Sakuya!
That's not fair!
You're totally seducing
him with those things!
I'm seducing him!
If you were any closer to
him, he'd be wearing you.
Would you guys chill out?
For your information, he's my...
I mean, he's...
What?
He's my...
Uh, never mind.
Look, I appreciate the offers, really.
But the thing is, she promised to
take me to the World Tree, so sorry.
Really?
Oh well, that is a shame.
Are you going there for a
little sightseeing, Leafa?
Or what?
I'm leaving the sylphs.
Or planning on it anyway.
But I want to return to
Sylvain at some point.
I just don't know when that's gonna be.
Not a problem, I understand.
Just make sure you come back, okay?
And bring your friend.
On the way back, stop by my place.
We'll throw you a party.
Thank you so much for
coming today, Leafa, Kirito.
If you hadn't been here to stop them,
the salamanders would have become
even more powerful than ever.
I'd like to pay you back somehow.
Oh no, it was nothing.
Hey, Sakuya, Alicia,
wasn't the point of you guys getting
together to make a try for the world tree?
Ultimately, yes, that was our goal.
If you're okay with it and it's no
trouble, we'd like to go with you.
We're kind of in a hurry
to get there, though.
Well, I can't see why not.
In fact, the truth is, we'd
be grateful to have you along.
But why are you in such
a hurry to get there?
She's not in a hurry.
I'm the one who has to get
to the top of the tree.
I think someone I know is
up there, waiting for me.
Hmm.
Is it Oberon, the Fairy King?
No.
It's not him.
It's someone I can't reach in real life.
But in here, I might be able to.
We want to help, but storming the tree
is going to take some time to set up.
We've got to gear up the
raiding party and stuff.
And that'll take us way
more than a few days. I see.
Never mind then.
I don't want to raid the tree like you.
I just want to get to the base
of it as soon as possible.
So it's cool.
We'll figure it out.
Oh, by the way...
Maybe this'll help you guys get
some new gear for your raid.
Whoa!
Saffia, look! Check it out!
A hundred thousand pieces of mithril yuld?
You don't want it?
You could build a castle
on Prime Land with this.
No, it's yours.
I don't need it anymore.
You are so awesome!
With this bag of loot, we've got
just about enough for new gear!
We'll get ready as fast as we can.
When we're set to go,
we'll message you, okay?
Yeah, you got it.
Thanks, guys!
We'll be seeing ya!
I don't know about you, but I
can't believe you pulled that off.
Oh, honestly, I thought I told
you no more flirting, Daddy.
But I wasn't flirting with anyone.
When those girls were clinging to you, I
noticed that your heart rate increased.
I'm a guy.
That's what happens when
girls get too close.
Seriously, what about me? I'm a girl.
Isn't that a problem?
No, you seem pretty safe to me, Leafa.
What do you mean safe?
I think what she means is most of the time
you don't really seem much like a girl.
Okay, whoa!
Say that again, I dare you!
No, like, like you're
easy to get along with.
I meant it in a good way.
Yeah, come on!
We still got a ways to
go before we get to Arun.
The sun's starting to go down.
Okay, I'm coming. Wait up!
.
One, three, two, three, two, nine.
Kirito, I promise you, I won't give up.
I'm going to push it up.
Highly highly out of this hand.
I will lift it up.
I will sing again.
I'm so
proud
of you.
I'm already late now.
I am not saying any other words.
Everything is so, all of you next time?
The end, the beginning, the beginning.
I am high, high, high.
I am holding my hand.
The light is the aim,
I am low, I am high.
Next time, the truth about Alfheim.